We often think of drawing as something that takes inborn talent, but this kind of thinking stems from our misclassification of drawing as, primarily, an art form rather than a tool for learning.
我们常常把绘画看作一件需要天赋的事，但这种想法源于我们错误地把绘画主要归为一种艺术形式，而不是一种学习工具。
Researchers, teachers, and artists are starting to see how drawing can positively impact a wide variety of skills and disciplines.
研究人员、教师和艺术家正开始认识到，绘画能给多种多样的技能和学科带来怎样的积极影响。
Most of us have spent some time drawing before, but at some point, most of us stop drawing.
我们大多数人以前都花过一些时间画画，但到了某个阶段，大多数人就不再画了。
There are people who don’t, obviously, and thank God for that: a world without designers and artists would be a very shabby one indeed.
显然，也有人并没有停止画画，这真是谢天谢地：没有设计师和艺术家的世界，确实会非常寒碜。
Some argue that so many adults have abandoned drawing because we’ve miscategorized it and given it a very narrow definition.
有人认为，之所以有这么多成年人放弃了画画，是因为我们把它归错了类，给它下了一个非常狭隘的定义。
In his book, Stick Figures: Drawing as a Human Practice, Professor D. B. Dowd argues that we have misfiled the significance of drawing because we see it as a professional skill instead of a personal capacity.
D.B.多德教授在《火柴人：作为人类实践的绘画》一书中认为，我们把绘画的意义归错了类，因为我们把绘画看作一种专业技能，而不是一种个人能力。
We mistakenly think of “good” drawings as those which work as recreations of the real world, as realistic illusions.
我们错误地把“好”的画看作那些能再现真实世界、以假乱真的画。
Rather, drawing should be recategorized as a symbolic tool.
相反，应该把绘画重新归类为一种符号工具。
Human beings have been drawing for 73,000 years.
人类画画已有73,000年。
It’s part of what it means to be human.
画画是人之所以为人的一部分。
We don’t have the strength of chimpanzees because we’ve given up animal strength to manipulate subtle instruments, like hammers, spears, and—later—pens and pencils.
我们之所以没有黑猩猩那样的力气，是因为我们放弃了动物般的力量，以便操作精巧的工具，比如锤子、长矛，以及后来的钢笔和铅笔。
The human hand is an extremely dense network of nerve endings.
人手是一张极其密集的神经末梢网络。
In many ways, human beings are built to draw.
在很多方面，人类天生就适合画画。
Some researchers argue that doodling activates the brain’s so-called default circuit—essentially, the areas of the brain responsible for maintaining a baseline level of activity in the absence of other stimuli.
一些研究人员认为，涂画会激活大脑中所谓的默认回路——本质上就是在没有其他刺激时，负责让大脑活动保持在基准水平的那些脑区。
Because of this, some believe that doodling during a boring lecture can help students pay attention.
正因为如此，有些人认为，听枯燥的讲座时涂画能帮助学生集中注意力。
In one study, participants were asked to listen to a list of names while either doodling or sitting still.
在一项研究中，研究人员要求参与者听一串名字，同时要么涂画，要么静坐不动。
Those who doodled remembered 29 percent more of the names than those who did not.
涂画的人记住的名字比没有涂画的人多29%。
There’s also evidence that drawing talent is based on how accurately someone perceives the world.
还有证据表明，绘画天赋基于一个人感知世界的准确程度。
The human visual system tends to misjudge size, shape, color, and angles, but artists perceive these qualities more accurately than non-artists.
人类的视觉系统往往会错判大小、形状、颜色和角度，而艺术家对这些特性的感知比非艺术家更准确。
Cultivating drawing talent can become an essential tool to improve people’s observational skills in fields where the visual is important.
在视觉因素很重要的领域，培养绘画天赋可以成为一种必不可少的工具，用来提高人们的观察技能。
Rather than think of drawing as a talent that some creative people are gifted in, we should consider it as a tool for seeing and understanding the world better—one that just so happens to double as an art form.
我们不应把绘画看作某些富有创造力的人天生具备的一种才能，而应把它看作一种工具，用来更好地观察和理解世界——只是这种工具恰好还兼作一种艺术形式。
Both absent-minded doodling and copying from life have been shown to positively affect your memory and visual perception, so complain loudly the next time your school board slashes the art department’s budget.
无论是心不在焉地涂画，还是对着实物写生，都已被证明能对你的记忆和视觉感知产生积极影响，所以下次你所在学区的教育委员会大幅削减美术部门的预算时，就大声抗议吧。